wjgnet.com 2017-02-16

# Baishideng Publishing Group

Last updated May 30, 2014

**Privacy policy**

Baishideng Publishing Group (BPG) is committed to the protection of your personal information. The privacy policy outlined here applies only to information collected by BPG through the www.wjgnet.com website.

**_Information We Collect_**

We will request personal information from you to establish your individual user profile that will support all online activities carried out as an author, editorial board member, or other related role. Information such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number and geographic locale are used as unique identifiers to allow access to certain content or to a secure site. All personal information is treated by BPG as strictly private and confidential. BPG will not disclose any personal information to third parties without your permission, unless required by law.

**_Cookies_**

Cookies and log files are automatically recorded when you visit our site. These data may include some or all of the following information: IP address, host name, domain name, browser version and platform, date and time of requests, and downloaded or viewed files. This information is used to measure and analyze traffic and usage of the www.wjgnet.com website and our digital products.

**_Making Changes to Your Information_**

Once you have created a user account on the www.wjgnet.com website, you can update your personal information at any time through your account settings.

This statement may be periodically updated.

If you have any concerns about how your information is being used or stored, please contact us by email at [bpgoffice@wjgnet.com](mailto:bpgoffice@wjgnet.com).
